民主是个好东西
You know, democracy is fantastic,
不过这玩意也太蠢了吧
but it is also fucking dull.
他们一点要分胜负的意思都没有
It doesn't even look like they're gonna break a tie.
Selina根本就不用来
Selina does not even have to be here.
苍天啊 她是不是要睡着了?
Oh, my God. Is she falling asleep?
不 她不能在电视直播的时候睡着
No, she cannot fall asleep on live TV.
不能在C-SPAN啊(政论直播台) 这样讽刺性太高了
Not on C-SPAN. The irony would be too huge.
别啊 别啊
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
你这是在挥手么? 她可不能望穿电视看到你哦
Are you really waving? She cannot see you through the TV.
一般人四岁左右就明白这个道理了
Most of us learn that when we're four.
我们可以打电话给她 振动会震醒她的
We can call her. The vibrations will wake her up.
不行 她没有睡着
No, she's not gonna fall asleep.
说不定只有我们注意到了这个事
It's probably just us who have noticed.
不是的 Clive 没有
No, Clive, no.
她没睡着
She is not falling asleep.
没有 只是那里很暖和而已
No, it is just very warm down there.
哇 头顿了一下 刚才她顿了一下 好啦
- Whoa, head jerk. Just head jerked. - Okay.
你确定订的是今天早上八点么?
You sure you set this meeting for 8:00 a.m. Today?
我确定吗?
Am I sure?
好吧 我错了 你当然确定啦
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Okay, of course you did.
必须的 请不要这样盯着我了
Of course. Please, stop staring at me like that.
用眼神剥光我的感觉 我是用眼神给你多穿点 Mike
- Undressing me with your eyes. - I'm adding more clothes, Mike.
绿色产业的火箭已经差不多到时候升空了 对吧?
Clean jobs almost ready for liftoff, right?
虽然细节上还需要一些打磨 不过是的
A little more detail work, but yes.
我觉得我们已经可以开始倒数了
I do think that we can start the countdown.
好的 那你穿好宇航服吧
Okay, well, get your spacesuits on.
说到宇航服
You know, speaking of spacesuits,
我在一个签书会上该遇到过Buzz Aldrin (著名宇航员 登月第二人 )
I met Buzz Aldrin at a book signing.
你知道他们宇航员最怕什么吗?
You know what really freaks those guys out?
在24小时之内连看17遍日出 好吧
Seeing 17 dawns in a matter of 24 hours. Okay.
早上好 早上好 女士
- Good morning. - Morning, ma'am.
我今天是什么日程 Sue?
How is my day looking, Sue?
你下午要去参加一个社区大学见面会
You have one community college meeting this afternoon.
这就没了? 是的
is that it? - Yes.
不 不 不 这样不对
No, no, no, no. That's not right.
好吧 等一分钟 如果你往下滚屏呢?
Uh, okay, wait a minute. What happens if you scroll down?
那要是往上滚呢? 那已经过去了 女士
- How about if you scroll up? - That's the past, ma'am.
他在这里干什么? Mike是你八点钟的议程
- What's he for? - Mike's your 8:00.
我们要讨论一下今晚你在消防员协会上的致辞
We're talking about your speech for the firefighter's association tonight.
Dan去哪了? 我找了他一早上了
- Hey, where is Dan? - I have been trying him all morning.
给我留了语音邮箱 呼喊他的名字
Left him a voicemail. Called him a name.
就是我们平常干的那样
- Just a little thing we do. - Mike!
我觉得吧 咱们应该开场讲个笑话
So here's what I'm thinking. We need to open with a funny joke.
开门见山
Solid narrative throughout it,
带到我真正想说的话题上 类似五佳吐槽那种级别的
into which I would like to pepper, like, five zingers.
没问题 我这里有几个金点子 好的
No problemo. McClintock gold. - Okay. Good.
我觉得开场我们可以稍微自嘲一下
I thought for the opener we'd do a little self-deprecating joke
说说在参议会上睡着了的事 不要
about your snooze in The Senate. - No.
不想听一下吗? 不想
want to hear it? - No.
好吧 没关系
Okay. Yeah, it doesn't matter.
这个是你第一个笑点
Okay, here you go, first home run.
消防员对他们的工作都很有热情
Firefighters have a passion for their work.
而纵火犯们则热爱点东西玩
Arsonists just have a burning desire.
你这个是笑话吗?
Is that even a joke?
是啊 这用了文字游戏或者是戏仿一类的手法
Yeah, it's a word play or a parody.
嗯... 好吧 没关系
- Mmm. - Okay, doesn't matter.
还有一个 好吧
got another one. - All right.
梯子在消防事业中显然是很重要的
Ladders, obviously germane to the firefighting business.
你就说消防员们总是在爬梯子
You go, firefighters are always climbing ladders
而政客们都...
and in politics you're always...
这个...我没认出来我写的是啥 但这个基本意思是说
and this, I don't even know what I wrote, but it's basically
你们是去一个什么地方来着...
you're taking steps to
不用梯子
get somewhere but without a ladder...
好吧 这个我一点也笑不出来
Yeah, this is not making me laugh at all.
那这个等成熟了再给你说
We'll bring that one back when it's ready.
好了 有天消防安全员问我...
Okay, fire safety guy asked me the other day,
然后你就换成自己的语气 我在床上抽烟吗?
and this is your voice... do I smoke in bed?
然后我就说 我从来都没什么好抱怨的
And I said, 'I've never had any complaints.'
口味太重了? 太重了?
Too shock? Too shock?
好吧 这还有一个半成品的想法
Okay, this is kind of a half an idea.
这个情景是如果你是一位消防员
All right, so the idea is if you're a fireman
要把湿毯子铺到什么东西上...
putting a wet blanket on something...
你迟到了 是的 而且我非常非常抱歉
- You are late. - Yes, and I am incredibly sorry.
我昨晚不是在家睡的 我就是...睡过头了
I was not in my own apartment last night. I just... I overslept.
好吧 迟到之后说你中风什么的还行
Okay, having a massive stroke is an excuse for coming in late to this office.
说你性福了是绝对不行的 Dan
Having sex is absolutely not, Dan.
说得对 女士 但是吧…
Quite right, ma'am. Although, in my defense,
我还以为你不在办公室 为什么?
- I didn't even think you'd be here. - Why?
呃 在白宫有一场关于财政责任提案的简报
Well, there's the briefing on the fiscal responsibility bill at the White House.
我以为你会在那边
I just assumed you'd be there.
他们没有邀请我 什么?!
I wasn't invited. What?
这个什么... 就现在
this is happening... - Right now.
去她娘的总统!
Fuck that potus.
他两周前国防预算简报的时候就没有邀请我
He did this with the defense budget briefing two weeks ago.
天哪 Amy在哪?
God. Where is Amy?
你戴着一个堵嘴的...
- You get a gag on top of... - Mike!
为什么我不知道这件事?!
Why didn't I know about this?!
我一定要去 他们不能把我晾在外面
I'm going. They can't keep me out of there.
女士 我在这里呢 你需要什么东西吗?
Hey, ma'am, I'm right here. Can I get you something?
你有旱冰鞋吗?
You got rollerblades?
我来了
I'm coming in.
好了
Okay.
很好
Good.
同志们好
Hi, guys.
财政责任 这太扯了
- Fiscal responsibility. - It's ridiculous.
你玩我呢吧? 这些人
Are you kidding me? Not one of those guys
都十年没自己出过午饭钱了吧 (讽刺各种工作餐)
has paid for their own lunch in like a decade.
我觉得我出席了就很表明态度
I think I made a big point by being there.
非常啊 不过我喘气声有点大
- Big point. - I was breathing really heavily, though.
不会有人注意的吧
You don't think anyone noticed that, do you?
Bob Lewis还有肺气肿呢
Bob Lewis has got emphysema.
听起来跟鼓风机一个效果
Sounds like a broken-down leaf blower.
确实是
He does.
这个确实是他给人的神奇印象
That is an actually uncanny impression of him.
副总统女士 怎么了?
Madam Vice President. - Yeah?
噢 嗨 Jonah 嘿 Jonah
- Oh, hi, Jonah. - Hey, Jonah.
你是来找我们的吗? 噢 不是的
- You coming to see us? - Oh, no.
我得请一个小时事假
I had to take a personal hour.
我和营养师有预约
I have a nutritionist appointment.
噢 你没事吧 会好起来的
- Oh, hope you're okay. - It'll be fine.
我是果糖不耐受
I'm fructose intolerant.
果糖? 就是水果里的糖分
Fructose? - Fruit sugars.
这很罕见 噢
- It's very rare. - Oh.
那祝你好运吧
Well, good luck with all that.
谢谢
Thank you.
你还以为他已经怪到最巅峰了
Just when you thought he couldn't get any weirder,
丫就怪上一层楼给你看 天哪
he did. - my God.
之前的事很抱歉 我以为你还在位子上呢
Oh, uh, sorry about earlier.
好吧 我现在要全体开会
I thought you were in the chair.
好的 你知道吗？ 我需要和每个人开个会议
Okay, you know what? I'm gonna need a meeting with everybody.
我要一杯咖啡
I need a coffee.
现在的问题是
Here's the deal.
总统在躲我
The President is avoiding me.
说不定他就是犯病呢 就跟Gary的脚一样
Maybe he's just flakey like Gary's feet.
不是的 我了解他 他很讨厌正面冲突
No, I know him. He hates confrontation,
显然现在就是他有什么要和我冲突的事了
and obviously there is something that he needs to confront me about.
那他还会明确地支持我的绿色产业提案么?
I mean, am I still getting unequivocal support on clean jobs?
这上面我需要白宫的可靠消息
I need some good, solid White House intel on this.
好的 白奸 对
- Yup, the whitegeist. - Right.
我来搞定 很好
- I'm on it. - Good.
好的 去吧 去吧 好的 好的
- Okay, please, please. - Okay. Okay.
我要看看今晚消防协会的这个事
I'm gonna check and see if this fireman thing tonight
都有哪报道了
is getting mentioned anywhere.
哇 你这是要自搜么? 是的
- Whoa, are you self-googling? - Yeah.
我们办公室里有人负责这个的啊 女士
We have guys in the office to do that, ma'am.
换我的话就不会搜索你的名字绰号什么的
I wouldn't search on your name or your nicknames, really.
我的绰号? Gary 我的绰号是什么?
My nicknames? Gary, what are my nicknames?
就是一些我们去搜博客的时候
There's just some nicknames that it's necessary
用到的小爱称而已
for us to search on to kind of pick up on blog coverage.
但是我的意思是 都有什么绰号? 呃 好吧
- But, I mean, like what? - Uh, okay.
有一个是和你支持法案相关的
There's one that has to do with the legislation you did
在公共场合母乳喂养
to support women breast feeding in public.
那是个好法案啊 那确实是个好法案
that Was good legislation. - It Was good legislation.
乳腺Meyer 不是吧
- Mammary Meyer. - Oh, please.
就像这个一样 还有别的?
Like that. - are There others?
噢 不是吧? 好吧
Oh, really? Okay.
吓夫人 希瑞公主 谎Meyer (希瑞为某古老卡通人物)
Grisly Madam, She-ra, Meyer the Liar,
蝙蝠窝 尿尿脸 (蝙蝠侠的基地)
the Batcave, Pissface.
西翼女巫 多嘴副总统 (西翼为白宫办公区所在地)
Wicked Witch of the West Wing, Veep Throat,
伏特加Meyer 没鸟范戴克 (Dick Van Dyke为著名喜剧演员)
VoldeMeyer, Dickless Van Dyke,
残颜赫本 金发女 无用Selina
Tawdry Hepburn, Blunder Woman, Selina Meh.
尿尿脸? 哈?
Pissface? Huh?
不 不是这个表情
No, not that one.
花瓶Selina 屎贝蒂
Vaselina, Betty Poop.
人们是因为你美貌与智慧并重而攻击你的
People attack you because they think you're beautiful and you're smart.
你很多绰号都是当初上Vogue封面的时候叫出来的
You got the most nicknames when you were on the cover of Vogue.
这个我记得 他们就是羡慕嫉妒恨 记得吗?
I remember that. They were just jealous. Remember that?
他们说你笑得巨傻 这个就别说了
- They called you Goofy Smile. - Let's not get into it.
完了 看起来你女朋友
Hmm, bummer. Looks like your girlfriend
没有当上议长的幕僚长啊
didn't get the chief of staff job with the speaker.
那我就不用买帽子了
Guess I don't have to buy a hat now.
帽子? 是婚礼吗?
Hat? Oh, wedding?
不
No.
我在Alice身上花了很多时间
Put a lot of time in on Alice.
我今天故意迟到就是要她相信
I was deliberately late for work because I wanted her
她比工作对我更重要
to believe that she was more important to me than my job.
她信了吗?
She fall for that?
我很怀疑 不过这种想法是很重要的
I doubt it. But it's the thought that counts.
她很欣赏我做出了骗她的姿态.
She appreciates the gesture of me trying to trick her into believing that.
真浪漫啊
That is so romantic.
可惜我们之间的好时光忽然就结束了
Sadly, the beautiful thing we had faded very suddenly
大概八分钟之前的样子 那下一位是谁?
- eight minutes ago. - So who's next?
谁家有利用价值的妹子
Which strategically useful young woman will get to witness
会见证你两小时的清晨护肤流程呢?
your two-hour morning skin care regime?
你喜欢这里吗? 我爱死这里了
You like this place? I love this place.
是的 都是干货
Yeah. No frills.
这里都是货真价实的哈
Not a single frill.
等一会他们把面包拿出来的时候 你仔细看
When they bring out the bread, you check it out.
那可是华丽丽的一大坨啊 相信我 都够一家人吃了
It is a fuckload of bread. Believe me, you could feed a family,
一家大胖子吃那么多面包都够了
like a fat family off the fuckload of bread alone.
我要来一杯橙汁 你要吗?
Think I'm gonna get an orange juice. You want one?
不要啊 没门 哥们 有果糖
Oh, no. No way, dude. Fructose.
我说绿色产业的事很不错哈
So clean jobs is looking pretty exciting.
那白宫怎么说呢? 他们和我们一样兴奋吗?
What about the White House? They as stoked as we are?
哥们 我都出了办公室了
Hey, man, yeah. I'm out of the office.
我不想说公事哈 噢 好吧 好吧
- I don't want to talk shop. - Oh, right, right, yeah.
冲口而出哈 我们这就是单纯的两个人在一起
Just punched out. Just two guys hanging.
是 是的 我喜欢和你一起
- Yeah. - Yeah, yeah. I like hanging with you.
谢了 哥们 好的
- Thanks, man. - Yeah.
惜Amy不喜欢(和你在一起)
It's too bad Amy doesn't.
可算了吧 她就是羡慕嫉妒恨而已
Please, she's just fucking jealous.
你们俩约会过之后你就行动了对吧?
I mean, come on, since you guys went out you've been getting action, right?
噢 疯狂的行动啊
Oh, mad action.
我的老二就跟卡普奇诺起泡器一样
I got a cock like a cappuccino frother.
大的那种哦 店里面用的那种 不是小的
One of the big ones. The industrial ones, not the little ones.
谢了 Joe
Thanks, Joe.
操 是的
Fuck, yeah.
看我说的吧? 这就是他妈的两个谷仓啊!
What did I tell you? That's like two grain silos fucked right there.
是啊 这就是正常的粮食群P活动
Yup, that's a regular granary gangbang.
对了 你有没有听Max Geldray在那瞎咧咧
Oh, dude, did you hear that fucking bullshit
说总统在躲着Selina来着?
that Max Geldray is saying that potus is avoiding Selina?
Max Geldray屁都不知道
Max Geldray knows shit about shit.
他的智囊就只有他自己的电脑而已
The only intel he has is on his fucking PC.
Intel也是微处理器的一个牌子哈 (和智囊同一个词)
Intel, that's a brand of microprocessor.
好笑话 总统知道绿色产业的事有戏
- Strong joke. - Potus, he knows clean jobs has traction.
Macauley参议员肯定会附议这个提案的
Senator Macauley, he'd sponsor that bill in a heartbeat.
他为了这个很性奋
He's got a big veiny boner for it.
我去 他们要我现在回西翼
Oh, shit. They need me back at the West Wing like now.
什么 他们要对谁宣战吗? 不是 事情更糟糕
- What, did we declare war? - No, it's worse.
官网的互动参观区挂了
Interactive tourist section of the website is down.
今晚在Labyrinth's有极端金属乐队表演
Hey, there's this extreme metal band playing over at Labyrinth's tonight.
就完全是噪音的那种 乐队连名字都没有
Just real fucked up noise. They don't even have a name.
你想去听吗? 是啊 哥们
- You want to check it out? - Yeah, man.
我们来整点大声的听吧 哥血液里流淌的全是金属
Let's go catch some decibels. You cut me, I bleed metal.
太好了 你想要点什么?
Great. - And What would you like?
我想要去别家餐厅吃饭
To eat at a different fucking restaurant.
那Mike的笑话都没用吗?
So Mike's jokes didn't work?
是的 消防员们是习惯看见有人垂死 Amy
Yeah. I mean, firefighters are used to seeing people die, Amy,
但不是那种死法
but not like that.
听着 我们必须恭喜Martin
Listen, we have got to congratulate Martin on this.
这个绿色产业提案的草案太棒了
I mean, this is such a great draft of the clean jobs bill.
是啊 该有的基本上都有了 我们只要...
Yeah, it's pretty much all here. We just need to...
提高实质性的处罚么? 关于违规处罚
Up the stakes substantially? Noncompliance penalties,
你不觉得处罚应该更重一些么?
don't you think those should be greater?
我觉得我们就应该这么办
I think we should just go for it.
我觉得我应该罚死这帮混蛋
I think we should just fine the fuckers
直到这帮混蛋被罚好为止 (罚和好都是fine)
till the fuckers aren't fine.
那也太不像话了吧
That was totally inappropriate.
不像话 不像话
Inappropriate. - Inappropriate.
顺便说一下 这已经不是第一次了
That's not the first time that that's happened, by the way.
他不应该表露感情的
He's not supposed to register emotion.
他就应该像个机器艺妓一样
He's supposed to be like a robot geisha.
我会处理的 好的
- I'll see to it. - Yeah.
可我们还是不知道法案
So we still don't know if this bill
是不是会得到总统的明确支持
has unequivocal support from potus.
Dan正在努力取得消息
Well, Dan is working intel on that.
嘿 嘿 Gary
- Hey. - Hey, Gary.
我要...我要回家了
I'm gonna head home.
如果可以的话 如果不需要我了的话 是 好
- If it's okay. If I'm not needed. - Yeah, sure.
包里是什么?
What's in the bag?
我今晚要上第一堂zumba舞课 (一种有氧健身舞)
Oh, I got my first zumba class tonight.
真好 我很兴奋
- Oh. Neat. - I'm excited.
我想Amy和我要工作到很晚
Amy and I are gonna be working pretty late, I think.
你能帮我个忙吗？
Would you do me a favor? Could you go and pick up
从Levin's取一下蟹饼么?
some of those takeout crab cakes from Levin's?
我爱死蟹饼了 是啊
I love those. - Yeah.
这样会打乱你的计划吗? 不会 女士
- That wouldn't spoil your plans, would it? - No, ma'am.
嘿 Gary 还有别的什么绰号?
Hey, Gary, what are some of the other nicknames?
不要啊 你这是受虐狂了
Oh, come on. This is masochism.
不是的 我脸皮很厚
No, it's not. I have very thick skin.
我只是感兴趣而已
I'm just interested, that's all.
只是各种VP缩写而已
It's just various V.P. things.
就是把V和P打头的词连起来搞笑
You know, like using the initials V.P. jokingly.
比方说呢? 徐娘半老
Like What? - Vaguely Personable.
伟哥禁用者 透明小内内
Viagra Prohibitor. Visible Panties.
伟哥禁用者?
Viagra Prohibitor?
为什么? 因为男人看了我都不需要用伟哥么?
Why, because when a guy's with me he doesn't need viagra?
不是
No.
意思是就算一个男的吃了药...
It means that even if a guy uses it...
也不管用?
It doesn't work?
他们是说这种理论上来说
They are saying that a prescription medication
不管男人年龄和健康状况
that is supposed to guarantee a strong and sustained erection
都可以保证强而持久勃起的处方药
in all men despite their age or their health
就因为我失效了吗?
is rendered ineffective by me?
你们再也不许搜我的绰号了
You know what? You no longer search on the nicknames.
你刚说你脸皮很厚的
- You said you had thick skin. - God, no.
等等 那V-Plif呢? 不 Gary
- Wait, what about V-Pilf? - No, Gary.
那可是恭维啊 你知道是什么意思吗?
That's flattering. You know what that means?
我爱泡的副总统
Vice President I Would Like to, you know, fool around with.
是来一炮的 好吧
fuck. - Okay.
啊! 这真他妈原生态啊
Ah! This is fucking primordial.
你知道吗? 你在itunes上都找不到这帮人
You know what? You can't find these guys on fucking iTunes.
你知道为什么吗? 因为他们没有名字吗?
- You know why? - 'Cause they don't have a name?
因为他们都他妈是非卖品
'Cause they're not for fucking sale.
你他妈好好听听
Fucking listen to this.
这就他妈的像是花栗鼠
This is fucking like being operated on by a chimp
在拿锯子锯东西似的 太先锋了
with a hard-on and a hacksaw. Radical stuff.
对 这就是我对绿色产业法案的感觉
Yeah. That's exactly how I feel about the clean jobs legislation.
总统说没说这个议程能走多远?
Has potus said anything about how high the agenda's gonna go?
所有的意见都很好 我明天去开会
All noises are good. I'm in a meeting tomorrow
肯定会讨论这个事的 我会给你打电话的
and it's definitely gonna get discussed. I'll call you.
那就太好了 哥们 谢了
That would be awesome, man. Thank you. That's great.
你先去买这一轮酒 下一轮我来 还有拿点花生来
Pick up this round, I'll get the next one. And grab some nuts.
我把所有的矿物质都出汗出到短裤里去了
I'm sweating all my minerals into my shorts here.
记得搞点花生!
Get some fucking nuts!
你知道吗 我让Dan和Mike扮演了反对提案的恶魔
You know, I've asked Dan and Mike to play devil's advocate
模拟了一些争议
against this bill, assemble some arguments.
就是人们反对提案的时候说的那些话
You know, what people might say against it and stuff.
Dan很适合
Dan is a great choice.
他已经是恶魔代言人了
He is already a huge advocate of the devil's.
总统眼下需要一些成绩
Potus needs some successes right now.
如果他近期还不能解决好经济问题的话
He doesn't fix the economy soon,
航天局就得给他造个逃生舱了
NASA's gonna have to build him an escape pod.
他怎么能搞成这样的?
I mean, how has he let this happen?
天哪 如果我是... 嗯 嗯
- God, if I were... - Mm-mmm.
别说什么 如果我是总统的话...
Don't say, if I were President.
这是副总统的大忌 好吧
- It's the V.P. bear trap. - Okay.
那我就不说 我光想好了
I won't say it. I'll just think it.
谢谢你工作到这么晚 Amy.
Thanks for working late tonight, Amy.
别想着明天一定要早到什么的
Don't feel like you have to come in early tomorrow.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
但是你会早到的 对吧?
But you will come in early, right?
当然了 好的
of course. - Yeah.
完了 Sidney Purcell 我们是不是应该走另一边?
Shit, Sidney Purcell. Should we go another way?
不 我才不怕什么石油游说人
No, I'm not scared of oil lobbyists.
我只怕两样东西 对 疯子和老年痴呆症
- I'm only scared of two things. - Yeah, bats and Alzheimer's.
好记性 Sidney Purcell
Yeah, well remembered. Sidney Purcell.
副总统女士 见到你真高兴
Madam Vice President. So good to see you.
你猜我们刚才在做什么?
Guess what we were just doing?
我们正在给绿色产业的最新草案润色呢
Just polishing up the latest draft of clean jobs.
你知道的 我是石油界出身的 但是这不意味着
You know, I am from oil, but that doesn't mean that I don't care deeply
我就不关心我孩子的将来 孩子们当然还是有未来的
about my children's future and, of course, their children's future.
说到孩子嘛 我得走了
Speaking of children, I've got to go.
Catherine还在等着和我视频呢
Catherine is waiting to Skype with me.
和您会面总是这么愉快 副总统女士
Great seeing you, as always, madam Vice President.
好的 保重 再会
- Okay, take care. - Bye-bye.
我没孩子
I don't have any children.
倒有个侄女 可我恨死她了
I have a niece but I fucking hate her.
真有爱心 我得回家去了
How charming. I need to be getting home.
恕我直言 如果你认为你们的这项议案能通过
I wanted to tell you if you think that this bill of yours is gonna go the distance,
那你的愚蠢真心超出了我的预计
than you must be even stupider than I think you are.
我得说 你有边缘性人格障碍
And I should tell you, I think you're borderline developmentally disabled.
这项议案就他妈是个奇耻大辱
This bill is a fucking disgrace
我要亲眼看着它
and I'm gonna see to it personally
像个臭婊子一样被吞进木片机里绞得粉碎
that it gets chewed up like a dead prostitute in a wood chipper.
只是想告诉你一声
Just wanted to let you know.
准备好了吗 地下重金属男?
You sure you're ready, Mr. Thrash Metal?
听说你昨晚只睡了两小时
Heard you only got two hours of sleep last night.
是啊 你起来上了好几回厕所呢吧 Mike
Yeah, well, with how many times you've got to get up and pee, Mike,
咱俩扯平了
I think we're about even.
嘿 你们读过刚完成的绿色产业草案了吗
Hey, have you boys read the latest draft of clean jobs?
是的 女士
Yes, ma'am.
也就是说你们已经有成熟的意见了?
Okay, so you've got your critiques all prepared?
嗯啊 谁先来?
- Mm-hmm. - Who's gonna go first?
女士优先
Ladies first.
有话直说 用不着扭扭捏捏
So you can be harsh. You don't need to hold back or anything.
当然
Sure.
这是阶级迫害
This is class genocide.
这是...你说这是...什么?
This is... this... um, huh?
这是富裕的白人和他们富裕的白人领袖
This is rich white people and their rich white champion
Selina Meyer为了让自己高枕无忧
Selina Meyer demanding an unproven solution
对一个不现实的问题给出的不现实的解决方案
to an unproven problem so they can sleep better at night.
谁为大型污染企业工作?
Who works for large polluting companies?
普通的蓝领阶层
Ordinary blue collar Americans.
谁会遭解雇或减薪来为这些税赋买单?
Who will get fired or have their wages cut to pay for these taxes?
普通的父母
Ordinary moms and dads.
谁会是最终的受害者?
Who will suffer when these companies are no longer competitive
一旦这些公司在你高昂的税赋和罚金下惨淡经营
because of your high taxes and noncompliance penalties.
这是冷血 阴险的 阶级迫害
This is cold, calculated, class genocide
其始作俑者要么是魔鬼
perpetrated by someone who is either evil
要么就该被安插在5150病区
or eligible to be held on a 5150
精神康复中心的
at a mental health facility.
为你羞耻 Selina Meyer
Shame on you, Selina Meyer.
好吧 记住这个名字
Okay. - Remember that name.
再也不会有人想给自己的孩子起这个名字
No one will want to call their child by that name.
如今已经没人叫阿道夫了 很快也再不会有人叫Selina
There are no more Adolfs. Soon there will be no more Selinas.
你们面前的 是最后的Selina
You are looking at the last Selina.
就是她 毁掉了整个美国
The Selina who killed America.
Wow.
噢 天呐 Dan
Oh, my God, Dan.
再也没人叫Selina? 好了
No more Selinas? - Okay.
住口 好吗 没人问你的意见
Quiet, okay? I don't need to hear you.
Mike?
Oh.
我的核心看法是 我没怎么看懂
My chief criticism is that I don't fully understand it.
如果我看不懂... 行了行了 干得好 蠢货
- If I don't understand it... - All right, good job, dummy.
坐下吧
Sit down.
Selina人呢? 她用完午餐 正在回来的路上
- Where's Selina? - She's on her way back from lunch.
你知道那趟去巴黎的行程么?
You know that trip to Paris?
嗯哼 成行了
- Uh-huh. - It's on.
不是吧! 是的
- No! - Yeah.
Amy 我有个问题问你
Oh, Amy, I have a quick q for you to a.
快问 在日程分级中
- Quickly, then. - In diary hierarchy,
出席国资委会议
does the national resource committee meeting
优先于慰问儿童协会?
trump the care for children's association?
没错 好的 我会砍了儿童这条
- Yes. - Okay, I will kill the children.
你知道在巴黎穿什么最合适么 就是你那身粉色紧身裙
You know what would be perfect in Paris is that pink jacket you have.
女士! 女士! 大事不好了
Ma'am! Ma'am! It's a fucking disaster.
怎么了? 能有什么事啊
What is? It could be a lot of things.
总统急于通过财政责任法案
The President is very eager to get the fiscal responsibility bill through.
非常迫切以至于... 妈的 不是吧
- So eager that... - Oh, shit, no.
他希望集全力于这项议案
He wants all focus to be on that bill.
因而搁置了其余五项提案
He's dropped five other pieces of legislation.
不 绿色产业恰在其中
No. - clean jobs is one of them.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
我的绿色产业? 没错
my clean jobs? - Yeah.
狗娘养的
Oh, son of a bitch.
总统他他妈的就是个气死人的狗杂种
That president, he is a suffocating son of a bitch.
行了行了
It's okay.
之前怎么一点消息都没有?
Had we not heard anything about this?
博客上先前确实有些动作
Apparently there were rumblings in the blogs.
我们为什么没看到?
Why weren't we on it?
他们用的是绰号 所以我们才没搜到
They used a nickname, ma'am, and we were not searching on it.
什么绰号? 不明Meyer女士
Which one? - Mrs. DoubtMeyer.
从没听你提过啊
Well, you never mentioned that one.
这说明您有那么点儿小困惑
Yeah, that means you're kind of slightly confused.
还有些男子气概
You're oddly masculine.
真够恶毒的
It's a shitty nickname.
听着 我接受不了
Well, I'm just not gonna accept this.
噢 天呐 要是我参加了那些弱智的 环特区Segway之旅
Oh, my God. I'd have more power in my hands
没准就能拥有更多权力了
if I joined one of those moronic Segway tours of D.C.
你们知道这对我造成了多大损失吗
I mean, do you have any idea what I have lost here today?
知道吗 嗯?
Do you? Really?
不说话是吧?
Are you not gonna say anything?
天呐!
Jesus!
Dan 你男朋友知道这回事儿么?
Dan, did your boyfriend know anything about this?
我有努力利用Jonah获取情报
I was trying to use Jonah for intelligence.
这就跟拿羊角包
That's like trying to use a croissant
当假阳具一样 我以为...
as a fucking dildo. - I thought...
省省吧 说白了就是
No, no, no. Let me be more clear.
偷鸡不成蚀把米!
It doesn't do the job and it makes a fucking mess!
请出去
Get out of my office.
Gary! 是 女士?
- Gary! - Yes, ma'am? Yes, ma'am?
我需要点什么 好的 是什么特殊的东西吗
- I need something. - Okay, is there anything specific?
我他妈不知道 我就是需要点什么
I don't fucking know. I just need something.
你知道我打算做什么吗
I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
我这就打电话给那个傻逼总统
I'm gonna call that stupid potus myself.
不开玩笑 我要让他收回他的狗屁决定
Seriously, I'm gonna tell him to shove it up his ass.
我觉得他没有任何理由...
I don't see any reason...
女士 我们先静观其变 好吗
Ma'am, why don't we just wait this out, okay?
先静观其变?
Why don't we just wait this out?
这就是你的建议?
Is that what you're gonna suggest?
要是跟你一块儿困在着火的楼里我就完了 Mike
Remind me never to get trapped inside a burning building with you, Mike.
我很擅长应对火灾 女士 打扰一下
- I'm very good in a fire. - Ma'am, if I may.
我有个主意 我们不如去找一位友善的参议员
I think I have an idea. What if we went to a friendly senator
提议由他将绿色产业中的主要内容...
and suggested that he or she take the best parts of clean jobs...
污染制造者制裁...环保企业税赋减免...
the sanctions on polluters, tax breaks for the good guys...
作为财政责任法案的
then added that as an amendment
修正案添加进去?
to the fiscal responsibility bill?
这样一来 就相当于通过了绿色产业 不是吗?
Well, that would get the meat of clean jobs through, wouldn't it?
但是这会忤逆总统的意愿
It would also mean we'd go against the President's wishes.
这是挑衅 女士 是啊
- That's provocative, ma'am. - Yeah.
我正想找人挑衅呢
Well, I feel like provoking someone.
真心的 Mike
I really do, Mike.
我全身上下都是挑衅因子
I'm feeling very fucking provocative.
我发现了 女士
I'm aware of that, ma'am.
总统不会高兴的 我现在就敢断言
The President won't like that. I can tell you that right now.
这是个陷阱 我知道 你说得对
- This is the bear trap. - I know, you're right.
我们不能这么做 是不是? 我们不能
We can't do this. Can we? We can't.
只要我们想有什么不能做的
We can do anything we want if we really want to.
你当这是拍电影呢? 美食 祈祷和恋爱?
What is this? Eat, Pray, fucking Love?
听我解释 我不能
- Give me a minute. - I can't be seen
背着总统偷偷干涉立法
sneaking through legislation behind the President's back.
太疯狂了 会被视作背叛
I mean, that would be insane. It would be disloyal.
女士 Macauley议员很欣赏这项法案 他会同意我们的做法
Ma'am, Senator Macauley loves this bill and he may decide to do it anyway.
听着 如果Macauley议员自愿这么做
Well, if Senator Macauley wants to do it himself,
那就万事大吉 明白吗
then that's great, you know?
但是我不能被人知道干这事儿
It's just that I can't be seen doing it.
明白了吗
Okay? Okay?
女士 我给您买了点儿冰淇淋
Ma'am, I got you a little bit of ice cream.
我想你可能需要这个
I thought that might be just what you wanted.
正合我意
That is just exactly what I wanted.
能弄点儿生奶油来么? 当然 给我一分钟
- Would you get me some whipped cream? - Yeah, give me a minute.
我想告诉你 但是我不能
I wanted to tell you, but I couldn't
不知道你明白没
because I didn't know if you already knew,
我忠于总统
but my loyalty is with potus.
狗屁 你根本不知道他会反口绿色产业
Bullshit. You didn't know he was gonna roll over on clean jobs.
你屁都不知道 Dan 我知道
- You had no fucking idea. - Dan, I had a fucking idea.
你猜怎么着 Jonah? 我们以后不要见面了
You know what, Jonah? I don't think that we should see each other anymore.
别这样 对不起
come on. - Sorry.
你的意思是 就因为我跟总统
So you're saying that just because I'm not as close
没有你想的那么亲近
to potus as you thought I was,
我们就不能在一起了?
that means that we can't hang out anymore?
我的意思是 大猩猩同志
What I'm saying, you fucking ape,
你他妈就是个彻头彻尾的废物
is that you are a useless waste of fucking carbon.
我本来还想利用你一下
I've been trying to cynically use you,
结果你他妈连点利用价值的没有
but you're so fucking low-rent, you can't even be exploited.
还有 上菜上这么大份的餐厅
Not to mention the fact any restaurant that serves anything in a fuckload
绝对算不上什么好地方
is not a nice restaurant.
刚才的面包是狗吃了啊 混蛋?
Where is the bread at this place, asshole?
你 你这个纽约郊区的傻逼... 瞧瞧啊
- And you, you upstate New York dickshit... - Watch it.
怎么了 老子说的就是纽约郊区
Yeah, I'll talk about upstate New York.
你们他妈的还当自己是纽约人 你们压根儿不是
You guys think you're fucking New York, but you're not.
瞧瞧你邋里邋遢满脸胡茬
And you with your perpetual 5:00 shadow,
我根本不想和你在一起
you're not that great to be around.
我讨厌你 Dan
I don't like you, Dan.
是吗 我倒觉得你有点儿喜欢我 Jonah
Really? I think you do. I think you're a little sweet on me, Jonah.
所以你才会这么生气
That's why you're so upset.
你知道么 Dan?
You know what, Dan?
你他妈就是根老二
You're a fucking dick.
晚上睡觉的时候当心点儿 混蛋
Well, careful when you go to sleep tonight, asshole.
没准我会带着一大包橘子
Maybe I'll sneak into your apartment with a bag of oranges
溜进你的公寓里吃死你
and fructose you to death.
我们该从巴黎给总统寄张明信片
Hey, we should send potus a postcard from Paris.
收回你的狗屁决定用法语怎么说?
What's the French for shove it up your ass?
说实话我有点儿怕巴黎女人
God, Parisian women really intimidate me.
为什么?
Why?
不知道 她们有点儿太巴黎了
I don't know. They're so Parisian.
你跟巴黎女人一样时髦
You're as stylish as any Parisian woman.
噢 谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
噢 你也是 谢谢
- Oh, so are you. - Thank you.
停顿得有点儿久了 是不是?
That took too long, didn't it?
我们去不了巴黎了 操
- We can't go to Paris. - Shit.
不 我们都安排好行程了
No, whoa, whoa. We got all those tours lined up.
你怎么又说... 安静 怎么了?
What are you talk... - be quiet. What?
他们预感参议院投票结果会是平局
They're anticipating another tied vote in the Senate.
您又得回去主持了
You need to head back to preside again.
敲小槌的时刻到了 哪项法案?
- It's gavel time. - What bill is it?
原话是该抡起大榔头了 我知道 我问你是哪项法案?
- That was a play on it's hammer time. - I know. What bill is it?
不是吧 是Macauley修正案?
No. No. It's the Macauley amendment?
是的 实质上就是绿色产业
Yeah. It's the meat of clean jobs.
您打算投支持还是反对?
Oh. - Which way are you gonna vote?
按照我的原则和良知的指引
The way that my principles and conscience tell me to go.
好吧
Okay.
你觉得该支持还是反对?
Which way do you think that should be?
我已经说过我的看法了
Look, you already know my feelings on this.
总统绝对不希望
The President does not want
绿色产业修正案通过
the clean jobs amendment passed in any form.
Dan 说句话
Dan, talk, please.
在平局的情况下 投支持
If it comes down to a tie, vote for.
你得支持自己的政策 是吗 你这么看?
you back your own policy. - Yeah? you think so?
不 是的
No. - Yes.
你真的希望我
So you are actually saying
毁了这项政策 毁了我们数月
that you want me to destroy the policy
甚至是数年的工作成果吗
that you and I have been working on for months,
想想我们的努力 Amy?
actually years if you think about it, Amy?
是的
Yes. - Wow.
好吧 说白了就是
All right, let me get this straight.
你 Dan 如此讨厌这项政策
So you, Dan, who are absolutely against this policy,
别解释 却想让我投支持票
don't say otherwise, you want me to vote for it.
而你 Amy 你赞同这项政策
And you, Amy, who love this policy,
却想让我投反对
you want me to vote against it.
是吗
Yeah?
这难道是什么狗屁诡异的镜中世界么
This is some weird ass through the looking glass shit right now.
投反对 投支持
Vote against. - Vote for.
女士 他们让你下去
Hey, ma'am. They need you on the floor.
哦 伙计 Ahem
Oh, boy. Ahem.
好吧 那么...
All right, well...
待会儿见了 同志们
See you later, folks.
祝我好运
Wish me luck.
是你让Macauley加上这则修正案的 是不是?
You got Macauley to add this amendment, didn't you?
我就知道是你 Macauley自己有脑子
I know you did. - Macauley is his own man.
如果是你干的
If you did this,
你就是违背了Selina的命令
you went against Selina's explicit orders
还将这整间办公室置于险境
and you have put this entire office into a salad spinner of fuck.
你干嘛呢 在查球赛比分?
What, are you checking your fantasy fucking football scores?
去你妈的
Get the fuck off it.
噢 伙计 她会怎么做?
Hey. Oh, man. What's she gonna do?
按我说的做
What I said.
本次投票 支持票50 反对票50
On this vote, the yeas are 50, the nays are 50.
参议院投票结果正反参半
The Senate being equally divided,
副总统投反对票
the Vice President votes in the negative
这项修正案未通过
and the amendment is not agreed to.
我参政就是为了做这些吗 Amy?
Is this what I came into politics to do, Amy?
我就是象征性地问问
It's a rhetorical question.
显然我参政不是为了这个
Obviously I didn't come into politics to do this.
告诉你个好消息
On a happy note, we reassigned
那个笑眯眯的特勤处人员被我们调走了
The smiling secret service guy. - Mmm.
你至少用不着担心带枪的傻笑白痴了
It's one less grinning idiot with a gun you have to worry about.
噢 天呐 什么事?
Oh, God, what?
很抱歉打扰您 女士 你已经打扰到我了
- Sorry to disturb you, ma'am. - And yet you are disturbing me.
总统非常焦虑 经过了近期的各种事件
Potus is anxious, after recent events,
您似乎还未意识到他希望您不要过问政府事务
that you don't feel he's trying to nudge you out of the process of government.
真是周到呢 不是吗Amy?
Oh, isn't that thoughtful, Amy?
他希望您能牵头开展一项非常重大
So he would like you to head up a program
又深得其心的项目
that is very important and very dear to his heart.
不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
你不会这么对我的
You do not do this to me.
别告诉我是肥胖项目 别告诉我是这个
Do not say that it is obesity. Do not say that to me.
是肥胖项目 不 不
- It's obesity. - No, no.
抱歉 女士 但您得负责减肥计划
I'm sorry, ma'am, but you have drawn the fat straw.
我会将相关文件下达给您的团队
I will have all the relevant documents forwarded onto your team.
好吧 你该洗洗睡了 出去吧
Okay, it's your bedtime. Get out of my office.
晚安
Good night.
天呐
Oh, God.
Amy.
说真的
I mean, seriously.
你能相信今天发生的这些事吗
Are you believing this fucking day?
我不得不亲手终结绿色产业
I had to pull the plug on clean jobs,
我正准备去巴黎 结果现在他又把肥胖项目丢给我
I'm about to go to France, and now he gives me obesity.
上帝啊 这还不算完
My God. I'll tell you something else, too.
这是故意的 Amy
This is deliberate, Amy.
总统知道 我一看到那些胖子...
The President knows how uncomfortable I am made...
就觉得恶心
by fat people.
想知道瘦身秘诀?
You want to know the secret to keeping weight off?
闭上你的臭嘴
Shut your fucking pie hole.
这能有多难? 这又不是让你研究火箭
How about that? It's not rocket science.
我不是营养师 对吗
I'm not a nutritionist, am I?
我不是 但我知道
No, I'm not. But I do know one thing.
你得放下玉米肠
You've got to put the corndog down,
你得脱胎换骨 你得行动起来
you've got to get up off your dead one, you've got to get moving.
行动起来可以作为这个项目的口号
Get moving might actually be a good slogan for this damn thing.
天呐 这无非就是因为软弱 就是因为软弱
Oh, my God. It's weakness. That's really all it is.
单纯直接 就是软弱
Pure and simple, it's weakness.
是自控能力
It's about self-control.
你不会在地铁上手淫 对不对 Amy?
You don't masturbate in the subway, do you, Amy?
你不会 你会在街上拉屎吗 Amy?
No, you don't. Do you shit in the street, Amy?
你当然不
No, of course you don't.
因为你能控制住自己
Because you've gotten ahold of yourself.
现在我要说什么? 我要说
And now I've got say what? I've got to say,
我是美国的副总统
I'm the Vice President of the United States.
放下杯型蛋糕 我的工作成了这个?
Put the cupcake down. That's now my job?
我...这...
I... it's...
操他妈的
Oh, for fuck's sakes.
你有过肥胖问题吗
Have you ever had a weight problem?
是的 我有
Yeah, I have.